Guide to the Trude B. Feldman papers, Circa 1941 - Circa 2013 MS2343
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Trude B. Feldman papers
circa 1941 - circa 2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Feldman, Trude B.
Schatz, Manny
MS2343
24 Linear Feet
This collection contains reporters notebooks, handwritten notes, correspondence, audio recordings, drafts, articles, and photographs relating to the work life of journalist Trude B. Feldman. The records span circa 1941 through circa 2013. Trude B. Feldman (1924- ) was a journalist and former member of both the White House and the State Department Press Corps. She wrote most regularly for McCall's and Ladies Home Journal, but has also been published in The New York Times, Washington Post and Wall Street Journal. Feldman interview every US president from Lyndon Johnson to George W. Bush and many vice presidents as well. In addition she interviewed every secetary of state from Dean Rusk to Colin Powell. Feldman has also extensively covered the Mideast especially Israel. One of her first reporting assignments was complete coverage and reporting on the 122 sessions of the trial of Adolph Eichmann in Jerusalem. Series one, two, five and eight are processed. The remainder of the collection is unprocessed and within each series there is almost no order. This collection will take more time to use. Please see staff for assistance.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Manny Schatz, 2015 August 31 (2015.046) Gift of Manny Schatz, 2017 December 15 (2017.075)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized into 8 series: Correspondence, Planners, reporters ntoebooks and diaries, Drafts, Articles, Recorded interviews, Handwriten notes, Photographs, and Adolph Eichmann trial
Scope and Contents
This collection contains reporters notebooks, handwritten notes, correspondence, audio recordings, drafts, articles, and photographs relating to the work life of journalist Trude B. Feldman. The records span circa 1941 through circa 2013.
Biographical / Historical
Trude B. Feldman (1924- ) was a journalist and former member of both the White House and the State Department Press Corps. She wrote most regularly for McCall's and Ladies Home Journal, but has also been published in The New York Times, Washington Post and Wall Street Journal. Feldman interview every US president from Lyndon Johnson to George W. Bush and many vice presidents as well. In addition she interviewed every secretary of state from Dean Rusk to Colin Powell. Feldman has also extensively covered the Mideast especially Israel. One of her first reporting assignments was complete coverage and reporting on the 122 sessions of the trial of Adolph Eichmann in Jerusalem.
Feldman was born August 13, 1924 and grew up in Hollywood California.
Israel -- Foreign policy; Holocaust, Jewish (1939-1945); Israel -- History; Israel -- Politics and government; Journalism; Eichmann, Adolf; Schatz, Manny
- Correspondence, 1959-2013; Series 1; 2 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically by year. Unknown dates are grouped together towards the end of the series.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence to and from freelance journalist Trude Feldman from the years Circa 1959-2013. As a correspondent to the White House, these correspondence include notable people such as, George W. Bush, George H.W. Bush, Barbara Bush, Eleanor Roosevelt, President and Mrs. Ford, President and Mrs. Carter, President Clinton, Secretary Clinton, President and Nancy Reagan, Harry Truman, Tipper Gore, Robert Kennedy and many others. In addition to these correspondence, there are many letters to and from multiple publishing companies.
  - Correspondence, 1959-1960; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1969; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1972; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1976; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1979; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1985; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1994; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1999; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2002; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2004; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2006; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2007-2008; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2009-2013; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Planners, reporters notebooks and diaries, 1941-2012; Series 2; 4 Linear Feet
  General
  Donor designated boxes 12, 19, 48 as having reporters notebooks. These are all boxes with the UP designation.
  This series contains notebooks, diaries, address books and appointment books from Trude Feldman. The documents date between 1941-2012. The notebooks contain interview notes from Feldman's time as a White House correspondant. Among the interview notes are more personal diary entries.
  In this series planners and notebooks were separated and then sorted by date. Any undated content are at the end of the series.
  - Planners, 1956-1959; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Planners, 1963-1968; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Planners, 1977-1979; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Planners, 1980-1983; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Planners, 1985-1989; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Planners, 1990-1999; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Planners, 2002; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Planners, 2003; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Planners, 2003-2009; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Planners, 2010-2012; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Address Books, Undated; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - High School Binder, 1941; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Reporters Notebooks, 1950; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Reporters Notebooks, 1964; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 1972-1979; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 1980-1987; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Reporters Notebooks, 1980-1987; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 1990-1999; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 1990-1999; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 2000-2011; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 2000-2011; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 2000-2011; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, 2000-2011; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Reporters Notebooks, Undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Reporters Notebooks/Diaries, Undated; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Drafts, 1960-1968; Series 3
  This series contains a small sample of the drafts written by Trude Feldman during her time as a journalist. These records are dated from 1960-1968.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Harry Belafont in Israel, Undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Sammy Davis Jr., Undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Adolph Eichmann trial, 1960; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Barry Goldwater, Circa 1964; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Bela Schick, 1968; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Frank Sinatra, 1963; Circa 1963 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Articles, 1941-2007; Series 4; 4.5 Linear Feet
  Series four contains three subseries: Newspaper articles, Magazine articles, and drafts. This series contains a selection of articles, and drafts for articles, from a variety of newspapers and magazines that Trude Feldman contributed during her long career.
  Arranged into three subseries: Newspaper articles, Magazine articles and drafts.
  - Newspaper articles, 1959-2007; Series 4 Subseries 1; 2.5 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains a selection of articles from between 1959-2007. Some newspapers that are included in this series are the Philadelphia Inquirer, the Washington Post, the Sacramento Bee and many more. This series also contains a large number of articles from Jewish publications and a few German newspapers.
    - Newspaper articles, 1963-2005; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1972-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper articles, 1971-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper articles, 1968-1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1972-2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper articles, 1972-1993; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper articles, 1963-1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1990-2003; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper articles, 1962-1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper articles, 1982-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper articles, 1984-2005; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1969-2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper articles, 1971-1993; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper articles, 2003-2007; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper articles, 1969-1990; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper articles, 1965-1990; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1978-2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper articles, 1959-1993; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper articles, 1977-1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Magazine articles, 1964-1999; Series 4 Subseries 2; 1 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains magazine articles written by Trude Feldman. Most of the articles come from McCall's Magazine and Ladies Home Journal from the years betwenn 1964-1999.
    - Magazine articles, 1976-1988; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Magazine articles, 1974-1988; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Magazine articles, 1977-1988; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Magazine articles, 1966-1976; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Magazine articles, 1964-1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Magazine articles, 1974-1982; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Magazine articles, 1974-1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Magazine articles, 1978-1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Magazine articles, 1974-1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Drafts, 1941-2007; Series 4 Subseries 3; 1 Linear Feet
    This series contains draft material for future articles, correspondence, government documents and photographs. The materials date between 1941-2007. The bulk of the material is from the 1960s to 2000s.
    - Drafts, 1973-1991; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Drafts, 1941-2003; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Drafts, 1979-2003; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Drafts, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Colin Powell notes/drafts, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Hillary Clinton multiple drafts, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Weekly compilation of Presidential documents, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Drafts, 1961-2005; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Reagan multiple drafts, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1979-2006; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, photos and briefings, 1979-2007; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Recorded interviews, 1964-2008; Series 5; 15.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains audiotapes, audiocassettes and VHS tapes containing interviews and speeches recorded by Trude Feldman. While a White House correspondent, Feldman recorded interviews and speeches given by former presidents, prime ministers, world leaders and Hollywood stars. The dates of the tapes are approximately 1964 to 2004. Some notable names include Presidents Bush, Clinton, Reagan, Nixon, Carter, Kennedy, Truman, Princess Margaret, Debbie Reynolds and Danny Kaye.
  The tapes are arranged by type of media and then alphabetically by last name or theme if there is no name.
  These themes include: Washington Conference on World Peace Through Law (1-3), Holocaust, Palestinian and Israeli Elections, and Peacekeepers to Bosnia.
  - Audiotapes (B-K), 1964-1970; Series 5 (Box 10)
  - Audiotapes (M-S), Undated; Series 5 (Box 11)
  - Audiotapes (T-W), 1965; Series 5 (Box 12)
  - Audiocassettes (A-B), 1989-1997; Series 5 (Box 13)
  - Audiocassettes (B-C), 1978-1992; Series 5 (Box 14)
  - Audiocassettes (C), 1978-1998; Series 5 (Box 15)
  - Audiocassettes (C-F), 1976-1999; Series 5 (Box 16)
  - Audiocassettes (F-K), 1975-1994; Series 5 (Box 17)
  - Audiocassettes (K-N), 1974-1994; Series 5 (Box 18)
  - Audiocassettes (N-R), 1988-1999; Series 5 (Box 19)
  - Audiocassettes (R), 1988-1998; Series 5 (Box 20)
  - Audiocassettes (R-W), 1977-2004; Series 5 (Box 21)
  - VHS, 1990-1999; Series 5 (Box 22)
  - Audio cassettes, 1977-2002; Series 5 (Box 49)
    This box contains three smaller boxes with audio cassettes of recordings done by Trude Feldman.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift of Don Gonyea 2019 October 18 (acc. 2019.093)
  - Audio cassettes, 2002-2008, undated; Series 5 (Box 50)
    This box contains three smaller boxes and 1 folder of audio cassettes. These were recorded by Trude Feldman.
- Handwritten notes, dates unknown; Series 6; 1 Linear Feet
  Box 37 is a selection of handwritten notes that were mixed in with Series 4 of this collection. The notes mostly pertain to her time as a White House correspondent.
  Arrangend in orginal order.
  - Handwritten notes, Undated; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Handwritten notes, Undated; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Handwritten notes, Undated; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Handwritten notes, Undated; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Handwritten notes, Undated; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Handwritten notes, Undated; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Photographs, Circa 1953-2009; Series 7
  This series contains photographs of political and entertainment industry people that Trude Feldman interviewed for her work as a journalist. Most if not all of the images are official White House or other government or news agency images.
  - James Baker, Circa 1992-1993; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Marion Barry, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Menachem Begin, Circa 1977-1993; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Harry Belefonte, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - David Ben-Gurion, Circa 1963-1973; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Jack Benny, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - George H.W. Bush, Circa 1981-1993; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - George W. Bush, Circa 2001-2009; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Laura Bush, Circa 2001-2009; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Jimmy Carter, Circa 1977-1981; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Rosalynn Carter, Circa 1977-1981; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Bill Clinton, Circa 1993-2001; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Hillary Clinton, Circa 1993-2001; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Mario Cuomo, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Richard Cardinal Cushing, 1965; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Raymond J. Donovan, Circa 1981-1985; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, Circa 1953-1969; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Stuart E. Eizenstat, Circa 1971-1995; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Paz Estensoro, 1963; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Gerald R. Ford, Circa 1974-1977; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Barry Goldwater, Circa 1985-1987; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Al Gore, Circa 1993-2001; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Alexander Haig, Circa 1981-2001; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Bob Hope, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson, Circa 1963-1969; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Claudia Alta "Lady Bird" Johnson, Circa 1963-1969; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Jack Kemp, Sanford Greenberg and William Brennan, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - John F. Kennedy, Circa 1960; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Edward Kennedy, Circa 1980-1995; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Saul Lieberman, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - George McGovern, Circa 1972-1981; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Golda Meir, Circa 1969-1978; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Edwin Meese, Circa 1982; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Hermann Merkin, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Richard M. Nixon, Circa 1969-1974; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Patricia Nixon, Circa 1969-1974; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Queen Noor, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Pope John Paul II, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Colin Powell, Circa 1993; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Yitzhak Rabin, Undated; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Condeleezza Rice, Circa 2005-2009; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Nelson Rockefeller and Happy Rockefeller, 1975; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Eleanor Rooseverlt, Circa 1960; Series 7 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Ronald Reagan, Circa 1981-1989; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Nancy Reagan and Raisa Gorbachev, Circa 1985; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Anwar Sadat, Circa 1970-1971; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Robert Servatius, 1961; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Danny Thomas, Undated; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Harry S. Truman, Circa 1965-1972; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - United States Presidents: Ronald Reagan, Richard Nixon, George H.W. Bush, and Gerald Ford, Circa 1990; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - George Wallace, Undated; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified images, Circa 1950-2005; Series 7 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Adolph Eichmann trial, circa 1960-1965; Series 8
  Arrangement maintained the original order from the donor, but that order does not appear to have been any true order to these records.
  Boxes 31-32 are ordered by the court document number. Other documents retain original order.
  This series contains historical materials from the years 1961-1965 pertaining to Feldman's coverage of the Adolf Eichmann trial in Israel. Series contains specific materials relating to Feldman's interviews with Eichmann, Eichmann's defense lawyer, Dr. Robert Servatius, and Eichmann's wife, Veronika Liebl. Also included in the materials are drafts of articles Feldman published during and after the trial and drafts of chapters of a book she planned to publish. In addition, there are many audio recordings about the trial. Finally, there are reserach materials such as newspaper articles from the trial and personal corespondences between Feldman and others concerning her work in Germany and Israel.
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [1/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [2/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [3/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [4/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [5/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [6/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [7/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [8/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [9/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [10/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [11/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [12/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [13/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [14/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [15/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [16/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [17/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Interview Notes and Chapter Drafts [18/18], Undated; Series 8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [1/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [2/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [3/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [4/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [5/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [6/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [7/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [8/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [9/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [10/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [11/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Interview Notes, Chapter Drafts, and Trial Materials [12/12], Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 2 Something about Me, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 4 Preparation, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 12 The Pressroom, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 15 Dr. Servatius to Me, 1961; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 16 Witness for Prosecution, Musmanno, Professor Gilbert, Dr. Gruber, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 18 The Guardian Angels Eranco Gottfelt, Heini Shmuel, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 19 Eichmann Talks to Me, Why I Decided to go to Germany, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 20 Post Eichmann Germany: Cologne, Munich, Brandt, Dowling, Munich Mayor and all people in Germany, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Notes of Diary To, Undated; Series 8 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Der Eichmann-Prozeß in der deutschen x öffentlichen Meinung, 1961; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Journal of the Middle East Societ, 1946; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - German court document, 1939; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Notes and direct replies from Dr. Servatius, Undated; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - District Court Document Minutes No. 18, 1961; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Interview notes and drafts, 1961; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Article drafts, Undated; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Drafts, Undated; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Drafts, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Drafts, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Eichmann news clippings, 1960; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 11)